worse than war is the very few of your city car you and history has never been
比战争更糟糕的是，您和历史上从未有过的城市汽车很少
free van met for city events like for the
免费面包车遇见了城市活动，例如
outbreak of blake's and the natural disasters got post doc
布雷克暴发和自然灾害发生在博士后
times it stinks at suffering and there we
它在痛苦中发臭，我们在那里
would doubt the actions to fix it there fair share of all chip and the
会怀疑将其修复在那里的所有芯片的公平份额的行动，
difficulties of life of the core of their philosophical and hard times of great
生活困难是他们哲学的核心和艰辛时期的艰辛
uncertainty many people start worrying about star stable costs dollars falling
不确定性许多人开始担心恒星稳定成本美元下跌
apart which is not only realistic some times aids in lifting the ball
分开，这不仅有时是现实的，有助于举起球
prospect or undergoing significant changes at hand or misfortune
前景或即将发生的重大变化或不幸
not knowing where this change leads to can be in a fracking
不知道这种变化会导致什么
the malfunction satchel profound thanks to say about dealing with external
故障挎包深表谢意，关于与外部打交道
circumstances and how to live peacefully in the face of hardship and the troubled
情况以及如何在艰难困苦中和平生活
future [Music]
未来[音乐]
living in a society in which must consumption is the norm and companies
生活在必须以消费为准则的社会中
brainwash into believing that we needed there product
洗脑，相信我们需要那里的产品
to feel complete the distinction between some white foil
感觉完全区别一些白色箔纸
not one was absolutely lesbi came invisible in huelva countries
在韦尔瓦国家，没有一个绝对是女同性恋者消失的
people riley concern him not even with their basic
人们赖利甚至不关心他
because the sorrow pass with from hard times sharla's channel
因为悲伤来自困难时期sharla的频道
is time to create clarity that site gets all priorities ar and learn to deal with
是时候让网站明确所有工作重点并学会处理了
uncertainty first of all it's essential to remember
不确定性首先要记住
the dark army of control and to be consiglio er of the fact that would only
黑暗的控制军，并且只想知道这一事实
control aro natchez agree your app it everyone's things like
控制aro natchez同意您的应用，每个人都喜欢
art by the property and reputation arnoud optimus one the economy the
财产和声誉的艺术arnoud最佳经济之一
clients for example there is your margin weekend about that we
客户，例如，您有一个周末的保证金
could lose a lot of money in the city market at chips and that harry came what
可能会在城市市场上以筹码损失很多钱，而哈利来了
from a story point of view by chinae happiness to these things in the first
从故事的角度看中国幸福到第一件事
place where all ready set or even on for disappointment
一切准备就绪甚至令人失望的地方
he effectively spent it and a quote the sphinx in control too
他有效地使用了它，并引用了狮身人面像在控制中
ar by nature free and restraints and obstructs with boxes modern control ar
ar本质上是自由的，带有盒子的约束和障碍物是现代控制ar
week sleeping with trains the longing to
与火车渴望的一周
others remember them that if you suppose that
其他人记得他们，如果你认为
things which shows lives by nature oh so free and that would be launched to
可以展现自然生命的事物，如此自由，它将被释放到
other girl then you will be handed and quote
另一个女孩，那么你将被递给报价
well the punch beg distinction between virtue of ice and in different virtue
好吧，一拳求出冰的美德与不同的美德之间的区别
and vice correspond with her own actions for example doing something for the
恶习与她自己的行为相对应，例如为
benefit of the community like profiling photo to the point elderly and be
社区的利益，例如向老人照像，
considered virtuous and train gear necessary
被认为是有道德的，并且火车装备是必要的
goods for exorbitant prices and be considered advice as to indifference arm
价格高昂的商品，并被视为有关冷漠的建议
riderhood sorbet examples of the sun 1111 disease weakness and poverty
太阳1111疾病弱点和贫穷的车手冰糕例子
in short indifference ar external circumstances
简而言之，漠不关心外部环境
darby under control now why is this important some correct risers
达比现在处于控制之下，为什么这个重要的一些正确的上升者
difficult times is that is indifference whistling some wet arabic tits
困难时期是那种冷漠地吹一些湿的阿拉伯山雀
that's that mean the varying care about the external finnchat already
那意味着已经对外部finnchat有了不同的关注
not necessarily s who not at least some of them to survive a lover
不一定是谁，至少没有其中一些人能在情人中生存
when facing hard times you might want to reconsider what we truly
面对困难时，您可能需要重新考虑我们真正的想法
new basic nothing like food a shelter for example
新的基本没有像食物一样的庇护所
so week and let go of the rest and stop worrying about them on the verge of
所以一周，放手休息，不要再担心它们了
economy collapse how important is it really should
经济崩溃真的应该有多重要
possess already chance of luxury goods and to what extent
已经拥有奢侈品的机会，以及到什么程度
dat socials terrace bring food to the table and protects as formulas
dat socials露台将食物带到餐桌上并作为配方进行保护
with thousands screamin 'out between rich and poor
富人和穷人之间有成千上万的尖叫声
the mori ar attached to the external to moriarty's mourns
附属于莫里亚蒂哀悼的外部
at the prospect of losing them the true faith that one can be perfectly happy
失去他们的真实信念是一个人可以完全幸福
and content with old and another essential story glass and concerns death
和满足于旧的和另一个必不可少的故事玻璃，并涉及死亡
and suffering this may sound land but at the end of
和遭受这听起来可能是土地，但在末日
the day death and suffering a part of nature in
死亡和遭受自然苦难的那一天
the west this is kai and see if the bow is death
西方，这是凯，看看弓是否是死亡
and something that there something tragic and needs to be avoided at all costs and
还有一些悲剧性的事情，需要不惜一切代价避免，
a comfortable lifeson minimize the amount of pain and suffering as much as
舒适的生活可以最大程度地减少痛苦和苦难
possible wat in hard times you might want to
在困难时期可能会遇到的麻烦
concealer that no one is entitled to go along and
没有人有权参加的遮瑕膏，
healthy life the history for planet is a blog your on
健康生活星球的历史是您的博客
animals and you my skill each other every day
动物和你我每天彼此的技能
children die adwords and the place of money hf of europe speculation
儿童死于adwords和欧洲投机活动的发源地
liveshow 2 modern humans left and right to be spared where the orphan of nature
liveshow 2现代人类左右两旁在大自然的孤儿中幸免
memento mori people who remembrance of death by remind yourself city death and
纪念死亡的记忆者，提醒自己城市死亡和
suffering marinus capable and inherent part of
遭受海事能力和固有的一部分
life you might find some tranquility in the idea that to first things at kan heb
生活中，您可能会在kan heb的第一件事上找到一些安宁
it was actually quite natural like Socratic
实际上很自然，就像苏格拉底式的
seneca that peacefully moreover i saw relief in des grottes des is release
塞内卡（Seneca），而且我和平地看到des grottes des的救济得以释放
from and another suddenly beyond the of suffering scanning text and impression
来自另一个突然超越痛苦的扫描文本和印象
story as to the peaceful rest in which will i be for work or if any one piece
关于和平休息的故事，我将在其中休息或工作，如果有的话
together the old also to peridot way inside
一起老还以橄榄石的方式进去
and quote from final piece of story cat fight for finding a sense of chrome
并从故事的最后一部分引述猫之争，以期找到一种铬的感觉
in the versity historie myself but we do not control
在我自己的大学历史上，但我们无法控制
ar destiny we can influence the future but your actions in the present wat de
命运，我们可以影响未来，但您在目前的行动中所采取的行动
richelle sars so deep and the ton of external circumstances
里切尔·萨尔（Ricelle sars）如此深刻，并有大量外部环境
for a while that is bot to guarantee types of wood, that economy can be better than expected
这是有一段时间的机器人来保证木材的类型，经济可以比预期的更好
gate how to join sarge alpes lesson above
门如何加入以上的sarge alpes课
team ethics and and to use numbers of people my boss ow
团队道德，并使用我老板所拥有的人数
and no single were i can change that zo white whale ourselves to just let go
我没有一个人能自己改变那只白鲸，让它放手
of the burden of the future knowing that whatever happens to your
知道将来发生的事情会给您带来未来的负担
a full control of the most powerful weapon available
完全控制最强大的武器
arlon faculty of week en koop there you can also cope with live de kut
星期en koop的arlon学院，在那里您还可以应对live de kut
news is that everything is a phlox and the born out of change light night and
消息是，一切都是福禄考，是光明之夜的诞生，
day and full and jumps so this too shall pass
天又满又跳，所以这也必定会过去
history show notes that people have enjoyed the hard fabric type's and that is
历史记录表明，人们喜欢硬织物类型，那就是
experience of measuring more humble more you may and more grateful for life dat
测量更多谦虚的经验，可能会更多，也更会感激人生
ever i outcome assets positive site entry car lease or
我是否获得过正面的资产进入网站租车资产或
what the future brinks de because i suah your power to make the
未来的边缘是什么，因为我说服了您使之成为现实的力量
best of it
最好的
thank you for watching [Music]
谢谢您的收看[音乐]